Something I hear quite often from folks is what do you expect them to do in relation to people who have held political office and who are no longer in office?
There's this like odd expectation that they should not be expected to do anything with the presence and power and visibility that they will always have having been in a political office that holds power, namely the presidency, the vice presidency.
Jimmy Carter is an actual great example of what I mean when I'm like, they should still be out here talking now that they are no longer in the White House.
They should be doing more of that.
AIPAC is not dedicated to peace.
They're dedicated to inducing the maximum support in America, in the White House, in the Congress and in the public media for whatever policies the Israeli government has.
Americans don't want to know and many Israelis don't want to know what is going on inside Palestine.
It's a terrible human rights persecution that is far transcends what any outsider would imagine.
And there are powerful political forces in America that prevents any objective analysis of the problem in the Holy Land.
This man was talking about AIPAC 25 years ago.
And y'all's beloved Democrats, Kamala, Cuomo, Gavin, Hakeem, Corey, yeah, they all not only take AIPAC money, but they support AIPAC.
They speak at their events.
They go to Israel.
And you wonder what we mean when we say Democrats are one wing on the same bird as them other ones.